(this["webpackJsonpjerocam-react-quiz"]=this["webpackJsonpjerocam-react-quiz"]||[]).push([[0],{50:function(e,t,r){},58:function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var s=r(0),n=r.n(s),a=r(16),i=r.n(a),o=(r(50),r(18)),c=r(15),l=r(39),u=r(73),h=r(81),b=r(74),d=r(79),j=r(82),w=r(80),C=r(75),m=r(76),x=r(77),O=r(78),g=r(38),p=r(36),f=r.n(p),Q=r(2),v=Object(g.a)({palette:{primary:{main:f.a[400]}}}),y=Object(u.a)({root:{background:"linear-gradient(45deg, #FE6B8B 30%, #FF8E53 90%)",boxShadow:"0 4px 8px 0 rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.2), 0 6px 20px 0 rgba(0, 0, 0, 0.19)",borderRadius:"4px",color:"white",height:"400px",width:"100%",maxWidth:960,margin:"3em 0","& h3":{fontSize:"2.2em",fontWeight:"500"},"& h4":{fontSize:"1.6em",fontWeight:"500",margin:"0.5em 0"}},btn:{margin:"0.5em",fontSize:"1.2em",padding:"0.5em 0"},btn2:{fontSize:"1.3em",padding:"0.5em 1em",margin:"2em 0",justifyContent:"center"}}),S=function(e,t){var r=e.questions,n=y(t),a=Object(s.useState)(0),i=Object(o.a)(a,2),c=i[0],l=i[1],u=Object(s.useState)(!1),d=Object(o.a)(u,2),j=d[0],w=d[1],g=Object(s.useState)(0),p=Object(o.a)(g,2),f=p[0],S=p[1];return Object(Q.jsx)(m.a,{className:n.root,children:j?Object(Q.jsx)(x.a,{container:!0,spacing:6,children:Object(Q.jsx)(x.a,{item:!0,xs:12,children:c>2?Object(Q.jsxs)(b.a,{variant:"h2",align:"center",children:["Your score total is ",c,Object(Q.jsx)("br",{}),Object(Q.jsx)("br",{}),"Congratulations!",Object(Q.jsx)("br",{}),"You passed the quiz!"]}):Object(Q.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(Q.jsxs)(b.a,{variant:"h2",align:"center",children:["Your score total is ",c,Object(Q.jsx)("br",{}),Object(Q.jsx)("br",{}),"Sorry! You did not pass the quiz!"]}),Object(Q.jsx)(h.a,{textAlign:"center",children:Object(Q.jsx)(C.a,{variant:"contained",color:"secondary",onClick:function(){return window.location.reload(!0)},className:n.btn2,children:"Try Again"})})]})})}):Object(Q.jsxs)(x.a,{container:!0,spacing:6,children:[Object(Q.jsxs)(x.a,{item:!0,xs:12,children:[Object(Q.jsxs)(b.a,{variant:"h4",component:"h4",children:["Question ",f+1,"/",r.length]}),Object(Q.jsx)(b.a,{variant:"h3",component:"h3",children:r[f].titleQuestion})]}),Object(Q.jsx)(x.a,{item:!0,xs:12,children:Object(Q.jsx)(x.a,{container:!0,spacing:2,children:Object(Q.jsx)(O.a,{theme:v,children:r[f].answerQuestion.map((function(e,t){return Object(Q.jsx)(x.a,{item:!0,xs:6,children:Object(Q.jsx)(C.a,{className:n.btn,variant:"contained",fullWidth:!0,color:"primary",onClick:function(){return function(e){e&&l(c+1);var t=f+1;t<r.length?S(t):w(!0)}(e.isCorrect)},children:e.answer},t)})}))})})})]})})},W=[{titleQuestion:"Find the sum of 111 + 222 + 333",answerQuestion:[{answer:"700",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"666",isCorrect:!0},{answer:"10",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"100",isCorrect:!1}]},{titleQuestion:"Subtract 457 from 832",answerQuestion:[{answer:"375",isCorrect:!0},{answer:"540",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"140",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"10",isCorrect:!1}]},{titleQuestion:"50 times 5 is equal to",answerQuestion:[{answer:"250",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"550",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"30",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"2500",isCorrect:!0}]},{titleQuestion:"Simplify : 3 + 6 x (5 + 4) \xf7 3 - 7",answerQuestion:[{answer:"0",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"56",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"14",isCorrect:!0},{answer:"10",isCorrect:!1}]}],z=[{titleQuestion:"In what year did the Western Roman Empire come to an end?",answerQuestion:[{answer:"19 CE",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"1200 CE",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"900 CE",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"476 CE",isCorrect:!0}]},{titleQuestion:"In 1641 which of England\u2019s American colonies became the first to recognize slavery as a legal institution?",answerQuestion:[{answer:"Massachusetts",isCorrect:!0},{answer:"California",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"New York",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"Boston",isCorrect:!1}]},{titleQuestion:"Who was Henry VIII\u2019s first wife?",answerQuestion:[{answer:"Anne of Cleves",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"Juana DArch",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"Catherine of Aragon",isCorrect:!0},{answer:"Jennifer Lopez",isCorrect:!1}]},{titleQuestion:"Who was the architect who rebuilt London after the Great Fire of 1666?",answerQuestion:[{answer:"Sir Christopher Wren",isCorrect:!0},{answer:"Sir Christopher Robin",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"Robin Hood",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"Arnold Swarzzenegger",isCorrect:!1}]}],k=[{titleQuestion:"Oil, natural gas and coal are examples of ________",answerQuestion:[{answer:"Fossil Fuels",isCorrect:!0},{answer:"Biofuels",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"Dinosaur resources",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"Renewable resources",isCorrect:!1}]},{titleQuestion:"An earthquake is any sudden shaking of the ground caused by the passage of seismic waves through Earth\u2019s rocks.",answerQuestion:[{answer:"True",isCorrect:!0},{answer:"False",isCorrect:!1}]},{titleQuestion:"2H2O \u2192 2H2 + O2",answerQuestion:[{answer:"Synthesis",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"Syntax",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"Decomposition",isCorrect:!0},{answer:"Nuclear Energy",isCorrect:!1}]},{titleQuestion:"Which of these chemical elements is heavier than iron?",answerQuestion:[{answer:"Gold",isCorrect:!0},{answer:"Carbon",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"Aluminium",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"Silver",isCorrect:!1}]}],F=[{titleQuestion:"Why is Big Data important?",answerQuestion:[{answer:"Because it may be analyzed to reveal patterns and trends",isCorrect:!0},{answer:"Because of its complexity",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"Because of its smarter and easier to load",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"Because of bussines",isCorrect:!1}]},{titleQuestion:"What kind of malware is designed to take advantage of a security hole before it is known?",answerQuestion:[{answer:"Zero-day exploit",isCorrect:!0},{answer:"Virus",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"Troya",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"Worm",isCorrect:!1}]},{titleQuestion:"What technology is used to make telephone calls over the Internet possible?",answerQuestion:[{answer:"Bluetooth",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"VoIP",isCorrect:!0},{answer:"Wifi",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"3G",isCorrect:!1}]},{titleQuestion:"Which computer language is the most widely used?",answerQuestion:[{answer:"Java",isCorrect:!0},{answer:"Python",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"JavaScript",isCorrect:!1},{answer:"C#",isCorrect:!1}]}];function B(e){var t=e.children,r=e.value,s=e.index,n=Object(l.a)(e,["children","value","index"]);return Object(Q.jsx)("div",Object(c.a)(Object(c.a)({role:"tabpanel",hidden:r!==s,id:"simple-tabpanel-".concat(s),"aria-labelledby":"simple-tab-".concat(s)},n),{},{children:r===s&&Object(Q.jsx)(h.a,{p:3,children:Object(Q.jsx)(b.a,{children:t})})}))}function q(e){return{id:"simple-tab-".concat(e),"aria-controls":"simple-tabpanel-".concat(e)}}var E=Object(u.a)({root:{flexGrow:1,height:"550px",width:"100%",maxWidth:"1000px",margin:"5em auto",border:"1px solid silver"},style:{"& .tab":{fontSize:"1.2em"}}});function N(){var e=E(),t=n.a.useState(0),r=Object(o.a)(t,2),s=r[0],a=r[1];return Object(Q.jsx)(n.a.Fragment,{children:Object(Q.jsxs)(d.a,{className:e.root,children:[Object(Q.jsxs)(j.a,{"aria-label":"simple tabs example",className:e.style,value:s,onChange:function(e,t){a(t)},indicatorColor:"secondary",textColor:"secondary",centered:!0,children:[Object(Q.jsx)(w.a,Object(c.a)({className:"tab",label:"History"},q(0))),Object(Q.jsx)(w.a,Object(c.a)({className:"tab",label:"Mathematics"},q(1))),Object(Q.jsx)(w.a,Object(c.a)({className:"tab",label:"Science"},q(2))),Object(Q.jsx)(w.a,Object(c.a)({className:"tab",label:"Technology"},q(3)))]}),Object(Q.jsx)(B,{value:s,index:0,children:Object(Q.jsx)(S,{questions:z})}),Object(Q.jsx)(B,{value:s,index:1,children:Object(Q.jsx)(S,{questions:W})}),Object(Q.jsx)(B,{value:s,index:2,children:Object(Q.jsx)(S,{questions:k})}),Object(Q.jsx)(B,{value:s,index:3,children:Object(Q.jsx)(S,{questions:F})})]})})}var A=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&r.e(3).then(r.bind(null,84)).then((function(t){var r=t.getCLS,s=t.getFID,n=t.getFCP,a=t.getLCP,i=t.getTTFB;r(e),s(e),n(e),a(e),i(e)}))};i.a.render(Object(Q.jsx)(n.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(Q.jsx)(N,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),A()}},[[58,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.013a715c.chunk.js.map